<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Spire]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib\media\favicon.png</url><title>Spire</title><link></link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 13:45:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib\rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 13:45:49 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator></dc:creator><item><title><![CDATA[Alpha]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>girl<br>
bloodline ability allows her to blend into shadow<br>
assassin]]></description><link>Characters\Alpha.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/Alpha.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 12:59:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gris]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Gris is the final antagonist, and is the creator of the <a data-href="Celestial Spire" href="\Locations\Spire\Celestial Spire.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Celestial Spire</a>, currently sleeping deep within the <a data-href="Sanctuary" href="\Locations\Sanctuary.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Sanctuary</a> on the <a data-href="The Floor of Light" href="\Locations\Floors\The Floor of Light.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Floor of Light</a>. Gris serves as the lifeline of the <a data-href="Celestial Spire" href="\Locations\Spire\Celestial Spire.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Celestial Spire</a>, managing things such as mana flow within floors and maintaining the barrier around the Spire that protects it things like erosion.<br><br>Gris was born in a village during the times of the <a data-href="Old World" href="\Locations\Old World.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Old World</a>, and lived the average life of a farmer. Gris had a burning passion for magic, and even though he was lacking in talent he practiced his magic whenever he was free. It was only Earth magic that Gris was capable of casting decently.<br>
Gris had two friends he was close to, <a data-href="Gris Friend 1" href="\Characters\Gris Friend 1.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Gris Friend 1</a> and <a data-href="Gris Friend 2" href="\Characters\Gris Friend 2.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Gris Friend 2</a>. Gris grew up spending his time with <a data-href="Gris Friend 1" href="\Characters\Gris Friend 1.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Gris Friend 1</a> and <a data-href="Gris Friend 2" href="\Characters\Gris Friend 2.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Gris Friend 2</a> playing and practicing magic together. However when he was a teenager, monsters attacked his village, burning it down and leaving no survivors. Gris and his friends were outside the village looking for herbs. When they came back, they looked for survivors but found none and were devastated. Since then, Gris and his friends put more effort into magic in hopes of having skills to protect each other if anything happened again.<br>
The group travelled to the capital city to become adventurers, forming a party and using their magic skills and accumulating experience in combat. At this point, Gris had magical ability of an average adventurer while <a data-href="Gris Friend 1" href="\Characters\Gris Friend 1.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Gris Friend 1</a> and <a data-href="Gris Friend 2" href="\Characters\Gris Friend 2.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Gris Friend 2</a> were a bit more skilled.<br>
While on a quest, the group encountered a monster far beyond the danger rating of the quest. As Gris was the weakest in the group, <a data-href="Gris Friend 1" href="\Characters\Gris Friend 1.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Gris Friend 1</a> and <a data-href="Gris Friend 2" href="\Characters\Gris Friend 2.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Gris Friend 2</a> protected him so that he could find some of their adventurer friends to assist in taking down the monster.<br>
When Gris returned with 4 of his adventurer friends, his friends were dead at the hands of the monsters. Enraged, Gris threw Earth spells at the monster, to little effect, and was protected by its attacks by a friend. His friends took the initiative in fighting the monster while Gris' mind was overtaken by the death of his friends, and this resulted in him releasing all his magic power and gaining a sudden spike in magic power.<br>
With the combined feelings of despair and the frenzy from unleashing all of his magic power, Gris' erupted out as his mind blacked out. When coming to, Gris saw the dead monster, and his adventurer friends, all impaled through with large spikes of stone. This sight sent Gris into further despair, and made him go mad seeing the blood on his hands.<br>
As time went on, Gris fought more and more monsters as revenge for the loss of the village and friends, and to take his mind of the sight of his magic running his friends through. Somewhere along the line, Gris stopped caring about accepting bounties and fought monsters for the sake of battle, using Earth magic the entire time. As he entered his old age, his Earth magic reached a peak where we was called the strongest mage.<br>
Having slain its ruler, he became the King of an ancient Kingdom, and ruled by fear. However he treated his subjects better than the previous King, and was generally liked among the citizens.<br>
As the monsters grew stronger, the lands were being overtaken and people lived in fear of monsters. Protected by Gris and his knights, the Kingdom had been the last remaining, and as it was being consumed by monsters, Gris casted an complex original spell to create the <a data-href="Celestial Spire" href="\Locations\Spire\Celestial Spire.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Celestial Spire</a>, a massive stone tower floating in the sky, and integrated himself into it, keeping himself alive in a comatose state as a final way to protect the Kingdom but also to achieve his desire to grow stronger by having people research and eventually resurrect him in an immortal body which he had researched but not been able to achieve.<br>
The people in the previous Kingdom were scattered within the tower, leading to the creation of Kingdoms and civilizations within each floor. As time passed, eventually the <a data-href="Old World" href="\Locations\Old World.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Old World</a> was decimated by war, monsters and the like and the only the <a data-href="Celestial Spire" href="\Locations\Spire\Celestial Spire.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Celestial Spire</a> existed.]]></description><link>Characters\Gris.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/Gris.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 06:45:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gris Friend 1]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Sibling of <a data-href="Gris Friend 2" href="\Characters\Gris Friend 2.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Gris Friend 2</a>]]></description><link>Characters\Gris Friend 1.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/Gris Friend 1.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 10:52:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gris Friend 2]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Sibling of <a data-href="Gris Friend 1" href="\Characters\Gris Friend 1.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Gris Friend 1</a>]]></description><link>Characters\Gris Friend 2.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/Gris Friend 2.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 10:52:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Iota]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Iota or Io is a 14 year old half human, half elf girl. Iota was an experimental subject at the <a data-href="The Lab" href="\Locations\Labyrinths\The Lab.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Lab</a> as a member of the <a data-href="Firsts" href="\Factions\Knights\Firsts.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Firsts</a>. Iota escaped when she was 13 years old, making her way down the floors to escape the <a data-href="Facility Workers" href="\Facility Workers" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Facility Workers</a>. Making her way down to the <a data-href="The Floor of Forest" href="\Locations\Floors\The Floor of Forest.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Floor of Forest</a> and meeting <a data-href="Scout" href="\Characters\Scout.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Scout</a>, who later became her best friend. When Iota turned 14, she resolved to climb the floors again, this time much stronger than before, to destroy the <a data-href="The Lab" href="\Locations\Labyrinths\The Lab.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Lab</a> and end the experiments occurring there.<br>White hair, red eyes from her mixed blood]]></description><link>Characters\Iota.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/Iota.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 15:52:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lab Spies]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>name tba<br>
Spies that do the dirty work for <a data-href="The Lab" href="\Locations\Labyrinths\The Lab.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Lab</a>. This includes smuggling monsters or children to be tested on, and protecting sensitive areas in <a data-href="The Lab" href="\Locations\Labyrinths\The Lab.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Lab</a> from intruders.]]></description><link>Characters\Lab Spies.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/Lab Spies.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 06:39:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ray]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Ray is a 13 year old half-dwarf boy living on the <a data-href="The Floor of Water" href="\Locations\Floors\The Floor of Water.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Floor of Water</a> in the <a data-href="Kingdom of Smiths" href="\Locations\Kingdoms\Kingdom of Smiths.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Kingdom of Smiths</a>, who is son of a dwarf and human. Ray is a bright and outgoing dwarf talented in smiting. He comes from the family of <a data-href="Ray Family" href="\Characters\Ray Family.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Ray Family</a>, a well known smithing family who directly serves the King. Ray's dwarf father has high hopes on him to succeed his position as Head Court Smith, however due to his mixed human blood, the people around him do not approve of him. With the pressure from his father and hatred from outside people, Ray's only desire is to leave the <a data-href="Kingdom of Smiths" href="\Locations\Kingdoms\Kingdom of Smiths.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Kingdom of Smiths</a> to lead his own life of adventure.]]></description><link>Characters\Ray.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/Ray.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 06:40:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ray Family]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>name tba]]></description><link>Characters\Ray Family.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/Ray Family.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 06:40:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Scout]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Scout is the protagonist, and is a 12 year old <a data-href="Beastman" href="\Beastman" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Beastman</a> cat girl. Scout is a kind, quiet girl who is an orphan living in the slums in the <a data-href="Kingdom" href="\Kingdom" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Kingdom</a> who is skilled with daggers and thievery. During her time in the <a data-href="Kingdom" href="\Kingdom" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Kingdom</a>, she meets <a data-href="Iota" href="\Characters\Iota.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Iota</a>, becoming best friends with her and learning Wind magic from her. When <a data-href="Iota" href="\Characters\Iota.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Iota</a> leaves for the upper floors suddenly, Scout is both sad and angry at her disappearance, and chases after her to learn about <a data-href="Iota" href="\Characters\Iota.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Iota</a>'s past and why she went back to the upper floors.<br><br>Scout grew up in a remote village on the <a data-href="The Floor of Forest" href="\Locations\Floors\The Floor of Forest.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Floor of Forest</a> and spent her early years as an average villager. However one day, her town was invaded by monsters and destroyed. During the invasion, her parents received a fatal wound while protecting Scout, and before succumbing to their wounds gave her the money they saved up along with a dagger, and told her to run to the <a data-href="Kingdom" href="\Kingdom" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Kingdom</a>, a place they always wanted her to go due to rumours of more opportunities and having a better life there.<br>
When Scout, who was 11 years old at this point, reached the <a data-href="Kingdom" href="\Kingdom" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Kingdom</a>, she resolved to become stronger and stay alive to honour her parents and village, however without knowing anyone or how things worked, the <a data-href="Kingdom" href="\Kingdom" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Kingdom</a> was very different to her home village and she quickly lost the money given to her by her parents and became an orphan living in the slums, learning to use her daggers and resorting to stealing in order to survive. Though Scout made friends with other orphans which she sometimes shared her food and ate meals with, she spent most of her time by herself, still in despair from the loss of her parents.<br>
Eventually, Scout finds <a data-href="Iota" href="\Characters\Iota.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Iota</a> emerging out of the <a data-href="Cross-Floor Magical Circle" href="\Cross-Floor Magical Circle" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Cross-Floor Magical Circle</a>, treating her wounds. They then became close friends, with Scout even discovering her aptitude for Wind magic and learning it from <a data-href="Iota" href="\Characters\Iota.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Iota</a>.]]></description><link>Characters\Scout.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/Scout.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 11:52:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Entity]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The Entity is a mysterious character residing on the <a data-href="The Floor of Fire" href="\Locations\Floors\The Floor of Fire.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Floor of Fire</a> that creates the monsters spawning on each floor. The Entity was born by a fusion of the barely-alive bodies of <a data-href="Gris Friend 1" href="\Characters\Gris Friend 1.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Gris Friend 1</a> and <a data-href="Gris Friend 2" href="\Characters\Gris Friend 2.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Gris Friend 2</a> and snuck onto the <a data-href="Celestial Spire" href="\Locations\Spire\Celestial Spire.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Celestial Spire</a> unnoticed by <a data-href="Gris" href="\Characters\Gris.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Gris</a>, who was in a comatose state. Though seemingly having a split personality between <a data-href="Gris Friend 1" href="\Characters\Gris Friend 1.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Gris Friend 1</a> and <a data-href="Gris Friend 2" href="\Characters\Gris Friend 2.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Gris Friend 2</a>, The Entity is in reality a separate creatures, a <a data-href="Slime" href="\Slime" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Slime</a> that is acting using the memories of their dead bodies.<br>
This creature has no mind of its own, simply following its desire to consume. However having consumed <a data-href="Gris Friend 1" href="\Characters\Gris Friend 1.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Gris Friend 1</a> and <a data-href="Gris Friend 2" href="\Characters\Gris Friend 2.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Gris Friend 2</a>, the high concentration of mana in their bodies influenced the creature, giving it a consciousness. Now, The Entity acts out its innate desire to consume by creating monsters to destroy the tower, with the goal of ending <a data-href="Gris" href="\Characters\Gris.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Gris</a>'s undying desire for power and letting him rest by killing him.]]></description><link>Characters\The Entity.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/The Entity.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Yuki]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Yuki is a 17 year old <a data-href="Snow Fox" href="\Snow Fox" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Snow Fox</a> <a data-href="Beastman" href="\Beastman" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Beastman</a> girl who lived on the <a data-href="The Floor of Ice" href="\Locations\Floors\The Floor of Ice.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Floor of Ice</a>. Being a <a data-href="Snow Fox" href="\Snow Fox" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Snow Fox</a> with longer lifespans, she looks like a 12 year old girl in human years, with a short stature with long white hair and pale skin, wearing Shrine Maiden-esque clothing. Yuki was living in a small village on the <a data-href="The Floor of Ice" href="\Locations\Floors\The Floor of Ice.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Floor of Ice</a> with her clan of Snow Foxes, when she met <a data-href="Iota" href="\Characters\Iota.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Iota</a> as she was travelling down the floors. Yuki took an interest in her and accompanied <a data-href="Iota" href="\Characters\Iota.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Iota</a>. As a <a data-href="Snow Fox" href="\Snow Fox" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Snow Fox</a> with <a data-href="Spirit" href="\Spirit" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Spirit</a> ancestors, she could transform into a spirit form, being a <a data-href="Snow Fox" href="\Snow Fox" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Snow Fox</a> or a fox with white fur and multiple tails. In this form, she could transform into a magical object, being a blue gem that <a data-href="Iota" href="\Characters\Iota.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Iota</a> wore as a necklace, which she later gave to <a data-href="Scout" href="\Characters\Scout.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Scout</a>, asking Yuki to protect her while <a data-href="Iota" href="\Characters\Iota.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Iota</a> travelled back up the floors.]]></description><link>Characters\Yuki.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/Yuki.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 12:11:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Battle Aura]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Battle Aura is a thick magical aura released by warriors that enshroud them.<br>
Battle Aura is usually used by warriors to enhance their abilities, and is a separate use of magic unrelated to spellcasting.<br>
Battle Aura is learnt by first learning to continuously emit magic from your body, then by concentrating and increasing the amount of magic released. Warriors usually learn to release magic first, then the process of enhancing your Battle Aura is done in conjunction with usual training, sometimes subconsciously.<br>
When well versed in using Battle Aura, warriors will also learn to extend this aura to cover their weapon and enhance its power or sharpness. It can also be used in less conventional ways, such as creating a large cloud of magic around you, to help in detecting multiple enemies around you.<br>
Battle Aura can provide substantial boosts in aspects such as strength, defence and speed. A strong Battle Aura can make a dull sword as effective as a sharp sword, or your skin as tough as iron armour.<br><br>Crystallisation is an application of magical integration and refers to the process of concentrating your Battle Aura enough to physically manifest it. Most warriors will only be able to use standard Battle Aura, some may be able to harden it or give it a physical shape but most of the time it will dissipate over time. Only the Warrior <a data-href="Legendary Warrior" href="\Legendary Warrior" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Legendary Warrior</a> has been known to manifest an aura so strong it has lasted for centuries since his death.<br>
Additionally, if a warrior has an inept talent for magic, they may unconsciously manifest that within their Battle Aura, giving it unique abilities such as inflicting a <a data-href="Curse" href="\Curse" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Curse</a> on anyone injured by their sword.]]></description><link>Combat\Battle Aura.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Combat/Battle Aura.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 04:30:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Adventurer's Guild]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Throughout the floors exist adventurer guild buildings, serving as branches of a unified organization connecting the different levels. It is thought the headquarters are located on the First Floor however in reality they are controlled from the shadows by nobles in the Shadow Floor.<br><br>Adventurers have ranks that go from S+ to E, which corresponds to the maximum job difficulty that they can accept. Higher ranked jobs are harder with higher chance of death but reward more.<br><br>People requiring help with anything including monster hunting can pay a sum (or on some occasions, a valuable item) to post a job request on the bulletin board. The guild will assign a rank that goes from S+ to E, corresponding to the minimum adventurer rank required to accept this job.<br>
The guild will take a small cut of the initial payment, then on completion, adventurers are given the job rewards.]]></description><link>Factions\Guilds\Adventurer&apos;s Guild.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Factions/Guilds/Adventurer&apos;s Guild.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 04:41:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Courier's Guild]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Couriers navigate between floors, are held in high regard as they connect the floors essentially, allowing for (slow) movement of goods between floors, movement of news etc. Fighters usually take jobs as an adventurer to complete jobs on their floor but if they have the strength to cross floors they may become Couriers due to the fame and money.<br>
Couriers are managed by the Courier's Guild.]]></description><link>Factions\Guilds\Courier&apos;s Guild.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Factions/Guilds/Courier&apos;s Guild.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 11:53:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Firsts]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The Firsts are the first generation of test subjects in the <a data-href="The Lab" href="\Locations\Labyrinths\The Lab.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Lab</a>. They received the most primitive treatments from the researchers, ranging from things such as having pure elf blood or monster blood injected into them.<br><br><a data-href="Iota" href="\Characters\Iota.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Iota</a><br>
<a data-href="Nu" href="\Characters\Nu.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Nu</a>]]></description><link>Factions\Knights\Firsts.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Factions/Knights/Firsts.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 11:06:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Floor of Fire]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Floor 7]]></description><link>Locations\Floors\The Floor of Fire.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Locations/Floors/The Floor of Fire.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 07:41:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Floor of Forest]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The Floor of Forest is the fifth floor of the Celestial Spire. Much of the floor consists of vivid green plains and hills, with large forests thriving.<br>
It is the largest floor<br><br><a data-href="Kingdom on Floor 5" href="\Locations\Kingdoms\Kingdom on Floor 5.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Kingdom on Floor 5</a>]]></description><link>Locations\Floors\The Floor of Forest.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Locations/Floors/The Floor of Forest.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 12:44:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Floor of Ice]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Floor 2<br>
Arctic region blanketed in snow and ice. Blizzards occur regularly and a massive waterfall wraps around the edge of the floor, spilling down into the lower floors. The cold is a sign high magic density, and the ice crystals blanketing the terrain contain large amounts of highly concentrated crystallised mana, being also used as a luxury item by nobles of the first floor.<br><br>The Kingdom of Ice<br><br>The labyrinth is a large frozen maze where large, dangerous monsters with a primal control over the ice await. The temperature is so low that the outside is warm in comparison, and it is said that when a blizzard occurs outside, then inside the labyrinth time stops momentarily. The monsters have a natural resistance to this and can therefore move when time stops, however even they do not know when time will stop exactly, except for perhaps some species of monsters which have an instinctual sense of the flow of time within the labyrinth.]]></description><link>Locations\Floors\The Floor of Ice.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Locations/Floors/The Floor of Ice.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 07:41:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Floor of Light]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Floor 1<br>
Houses the artificial elves and the experiment house. The elves are following their mission given to them by the tower's creator to create the ultimate magical being that will become a vessel for the tower's creator.]]></description><link>Locations\Floors\The Floor of Light.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Locations/Floors/The Floor of Light.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 07:41:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Floor of Sand]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Floor 6]]></description><link>Locations\Floors\The Floor of Sand.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Locations/Floors/The Floor of Sand.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 07:41:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Floor of Shadows]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Floor 3<br>
The Floor is a vast, barren wasteland cast in shadows and fog, and barely anyone goes there. This is a major challenge for people climbing the floors. It is extremely rare for anyone to survive this floor, a fact that deters people from climbing past this floor. Kingdom The Kingdom of Elezar (?), a mysterious kingdom with little known about it. The Kingdom is very secretive, and things like the population, culture are all unknown. The Kingdom has receded a large amount in size, and there is a large amount of ruins nearby which are the ruins of the Kingdom, which was once much larger when there was less fog and darkness, when the tower was created. Labyrinth Graveyard of Myths. It is said that when valiant warriors die, their soul ends up in the Graveyard of Myths training in eternal combat, waiting for the next living warrior to challenge them.]]></description><link>Locations\Floors\The Floor of Shadows.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Locations/Floors/The Floor of Shadows.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 07:41:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Floor of Water]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Floor 4<br>
Sort of oceanpunk? Blacksmith village. Water flowing down the side of floor onto the lower floors.  ]]></description><link>Locations\Floors\The Floor of Water.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Locations/Floors/The Floor of Water.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 07:41:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kingdom of Smiths]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>needs a name]]></description><link>Locations\Kingdoms\Kingdom of Smiths.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Locations/Kingdoms/Kingdom of Smiths.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 12:43:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kingdom on Floor 5]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>Locations\Kingdoms\Kingdom on Floor 5.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Locations/Kingdoms/Kingdom on Floor 5.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 12:43:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Lab]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The Labyrinth of the <a data-href="The Floor of Light" href="\Locations\Floors\The Floor of Light.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Floor of Light</a>. The Lab is a testing ground where researchers carry out experiments on test subjects. Their goal is to create a pure elf, beings with a perfect aptitude for magic of all elements, a naturally immense amount of mana and a long lifespan that far eclipsed the human lifespan. In other words, a vessel for <a data-href="Gris" href="\Characters\Gris.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Gris</a> the Creator to reincarnate to.<br>
The test subjects are made up of mostly children smuggled from lower floors, or birthed within the Facility. Test subjects with promising results or high potential are grouped and given special treatment, such as being given better food or sleeping quarters, but in exchange they have more experiments carried out on them.<br>
The first generation are dubbed the <a data-href="Firsts" href="\Factions\Knights\Firsts.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Firsts</a>.<br><br>The Lab was once a deadly maze with extremely dangerous monsters and traps, but was cleared by the <a data-href="Battalion" href="\Battalion" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Battalion</a> who defeated the <a data-href="Guardian" href="\Guardian" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Guardian</a> that protected the maze.<br>
Afterwards, the maze was named as the Lab and became a testing ground for researchers. The walls of the maze were torn down and the maze was transformed into a massive modern, almost sci-fi lab. Areas where monsters spawned were trapped so that any new monsters were immobilised to be used as research materials.<br>looks like a hexagon]]></description><link>Locations\Labyrinths\The Lab.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Locations/Labyrinths/The Lab.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 13:02:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Axis Circle]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Axis Circles are the <a data-href="Magic Circles" href="\Magic\Techniques\Magic Circles.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Magic Circles</a> on each floor that move people between floors. When interacting with the circle, a certain amount of mana is transferred depending on whether the user wants to ascend or descend a floor.<br>
One can descend instantly but ascending a floor will summon a <a data-href="Floor Guardians" href="\Monsters\Floor Guardians\Floor Guardians.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Floor Guardians</a> they must defeat first. When defeated, the magic circle will be activated, allowing the user to ascend the floor for a period of time before it automatically deactivates. Multiple people can ascend/descend at the same time. If the Axis Circle is already activated, other users do not need to fight the <a data-href="Floor Guardians" href="\Monsters\Floor Guardians\Floor Guardians.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Floor Guardians</a>.]]></description><link>Locations\Spire\Axis Circle.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Locations/Spire/Axis Circle.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 12:39:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Floors]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>An enormous stone tower created by the Great Mage. Comprised of several floors, each the size of a country to a continent. Among other things, each floor houses its own Kingdom and Labyrinth. Within each floor there is an <a data-href="Axis Circle" href="\Locations\Spire\Axis Circle.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Axis Circle</a> that allows for transportation between floors.<br>
Comprised of 7 floors, each floor around country to continent sized. Each floor contains among towns forests etc it's own Kingdom and Labyrinth.<br>
Water flowing down from the side of each floor, source being the Floor of Ice.<br><br>Floor 1 - <a data-href="The Floor of Light" href="\Locations\Floors\The Floor of Light.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Floor of Light</a><br>
Floor 2 - <a data-href="The Floor of Ice" href="\Locations\Floors\The Floor of Ice.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Floor of Ice</a><br>
Floor 3 - <a data-href="The Floor of Shadows" href="\Locations\Floors\The Floor of Shadows.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Floor of Shadows</a><br>
Floor 4 - <a data-href="The Floor of Water" href="\Locations\Floors\The Floor of Water.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Floor of Water</a><br>
Floor 5 - <a data-href="The Floor of Forest" href="\Locations\Floors\The Floor of Forest.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Floor of Forest</a><br>
Floor 6 - <a data-href="The Floor of Sand" href="\Locations\Floors\The Floor of Sand.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Floor of Sand</a><br>
Floor 7 - <a data-href="The Floor of Fire" href="\Locations\Floors\The Floor of Fire.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Floor of Fire</a>]]></description><link>Locations\Spire\Celestial Spire.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Locations/Spire/Celestial Spire.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 12:37:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Old World]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>Locations\Old World.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Locations/Old World.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 10:18:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sanctuary]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>Locations\Sanctuary.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Locations/Sanctuary.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 10:12:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Earth]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>Magic\Elements\Earth.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Magic/Elements/Earth.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 12:27:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fire]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>d]]></description><link>Magic\Elements\Fire.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Magic/Elements/Fire.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 12:27:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Water]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>Magic\Elements\Water.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Magic/Elements/Water.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 12:27:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Explosion]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>Magic\Spells\Explosion.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Magic/Spells/Explosion.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 10:04:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Explosion Fireball]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>Magic\Spells\Explosion Fireball.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Magic/Spells/Explosion Fireball.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 10:07:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fireball]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Fireball
Test<br>
';'<br>
mjjj<br>
lkkk;l
<br>lk;lk]]></description><link>Magic\Spells\Fireball.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Magic/Spells/Fireball.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:51:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stone Blast]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>Magic\Spells\Stone Blast.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Magic/Spells/Stone Blast.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 13:01:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Casting]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Casting is the standard way to activate magic. To cast magic spells, the caster must manipulate mana in certain ways to achieve their desired effect.<br>
A basic spell like <a data-href="Fireball" href="\Magic\Spells\Fireball.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Fireball</a> could be cast by collecting mana in your hand, forming it into a ball, infusing it with <a data-href="Fire" href="\Magic\Elements\Fire.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Fire</a> and releasing it towards the target.]]></description><link>Magic\Techniques\Casting.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Magic/Techniques/Casting.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 12:27:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Composition]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Composite magic combines spells to create new spells that involve multiple effects. These are harder to learn and use but are stronger than basic magic. An example is the <a data-href="Explosion Fireball" href="\Magic\Spells\Explosion Fireball.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Explosion Fireball</a> spell, created by combining the <a data-href="Fireball" href="\Magic\Spells\Fireball.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Fireball</a> spell with <a data-href="Explosion" href="\Magic\Spells\Explosion.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Explosion</a> magic.]]></description><link>Magic\Techniques\Composition.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Magic/Techniques/Composition.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 11:58:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Incantations]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Incantations are a newly-popularised way of spellcasting in which the spellcaster chants an incantation to cast magic.<br>
The incantation forms a mental image of the casting of the spell, which guides the user to subconsciously cast the spell.<br>
Spellcasters must first be skilled with basic mana manipulation before they can effectively use incantations, however afterwards using incantations is generally easier than the traditional way of learning spells without chanting, of manually manipulating mana to form and cast your spell.<br>
This ease of casting makes incantations popular in many magic academies where professors aim to teach more magic spells to students.<br>
On the other hand, chanted magic takes longer to cast and altering them takes more practice. Additionally, opponents may be able to recognise the incantation and therefore the spell, and counter it.<br>
Skilled spellcasters are able to shorten incantations or create their own, combating the disadvantages.]]></description><link>Magic\Techniques\Incantations.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Magic/Techniques/Incantations.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 11:58:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Magic Circles]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Magic circles store spells as an instruction format in the form of a 2D circle drawn on some surface. When mana is passed through the circle, instruction runes form the magic spell as it flows through the circle to produce a spell. Mana first passes through a "starting point" on the outer ring, through then the starting rune, then travels through the inner ring. Magic circles commonly have two outer rings with runes between them with lines inside the smaller ring that direct the flow of magic through a rune.<br>
Geometric paths are popular choices as these clearly and efficiently direct mana flow. Additional shapes have also been used such as pentagons in lieu of circles, but circles remain the popular choice due to their simple and efficient shape.]]></description><link>Magic\Techniques\Magic Circles.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Magic/Techniques/Magic Circles.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 11:59:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Materialisation]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Materialisation refers to the process of bringing magic to permanent form. An example of this would be creation magic that can create objects like stone.<br>
These can include objects, or even 'stored' magics which only require magic to be passed through them to activate spells without requiring mana manipulation beforehand or needing knowledge of the initial spell construction.<br>
An example is ocular magic which is magic that is stored in the eyes and can be activated on anything in the user's field of view. Over time, materialised magic stored in the body can integrate itself with the users genetic code and be passed genetically, resulting in certain clans with special abilities (not to be confused with genetic abilities that come from other factors like race).]]></description><link>Magic\Techniques\Materialisation.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Magic/Techniques/Materialisation.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 11:58:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Magic]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>In the <a data-href="Celestial Spire" href="\Locations\Spire\Celestial Spire.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Celestial Spire</a>, mysterious phenomena brought about by <a data-href="Mana" href="\Magic\Mana.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Mana</a> is called <a data-href="Magic" href="\Magic\Magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Magic</a> which can have various effects such as conjuring water or creating stone structures.<br><br>Various techniques are used to cast magic. These include:<br>
<br><a data-href="Casting" href="\Magic\Techniques\Casting.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Casting</a>
<br><a data-href="Composition" href="\Magic\Techniques\Composition.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Composition</a>
<br><a data-href="Incantations" href="\Magic\Techniques\Incantations.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Incantations</a>
<br><a data-href="Materialisation" href="\Magic\Techniques\Materialisation.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Materialisation</a>
<br><a data-href="Magic Circles" href="\Magic\Techniques\Magic Circles.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Magic Circles</a>
]]></description><link>Magic\Magic.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Magic/Magic.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 12:26:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mana]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Mana inhabits and flows through the body and be controlled and manipulate to cast magic with. People are born with varying amounts of mana, which can be increased as they practice magic.<br>
Mana can also be infused with basic elements, such as <a data-href="Water" href="\Magic\Elements\Water.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Water</a>, <a data-href="Earth" href="\Magic\Elements\Earth.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Earth</a>, <a data-href="Wind" href="\Magic\Elements\Wind.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Wind</a> or <a data-href="Fire" href="\Magic\Elements\Fire.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Fire</a>.<br>
People are born with a natural affinity towards one element (or multiple, on rare occasions) and may learn more later on.]]></description><link>Magic\Mana.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Magic/Mana.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 12:28:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Floor Guardians]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Floor Guardians are the guardians that guard the <a data-href="Axis Circle" href="\Locations\Spire\Axis Circle.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Axis Circle</a> of each floor. Floor Guardians are strong enemies made up by mana, who are generally stronger on higher floors.<br><br>Floor 1 -<br>
Floor 2 -<br>
Floor 3 - <a data-href="Ghost" href="\Monsters\Floor Guardians\Ghost.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Ghost</a><br>
Floor 4 -<br>
Floor 5 -<br>
Floor 6 -<br>
Floor 7 - ]]></description><link>Monsters\Floor Guardians\Floor Guardians.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Monsters/Floor Guardians/Floor Guardians.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 12:37:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ghost]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The <a data-href="Ghost" href="\Monsters\Floor Guardians\Ghost.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Ghost</a> is the <a data-href="Floor Guardians" href="\Monsters\Floor Guardians\Floor Guardians.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Floor Guardians</a> of Floor 3, <a data-href="The Floor of Shadows" href="\Locations\Floors\The Floor of Shadows.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Floor of Shadows</a>. The <a data-href="Ghost" href="\Monsters\Floor Guardians\Ghost.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Ghost</a> is a floating monster that looks like a large cloth draped over a person, with smoke emanating out of the bottom.]]></description><link>Monsters\Floor Guardians\Ghost.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Monsters/Floor Guardians/Ghost.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 12:39:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Arc 1]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Dual pov<br>
Iota and scout meet and bond<br>
Wheh iota arrived and recovering from wounds scout go steal<br>
Scout shows iota the orphanage<br>
Short sol, iota teaches scout magic<br>
Hint towards iota wanting to return<br>
Orphanage reminds iota of facility<br>
Event -&gt; orphanage attacked can show scout is strong ie below<br>
When scout gets good with magic iota decides to return<br>
Gives scout her necklace (Yuki)]]></description><link>Timeline\Arc 1.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Timeline/Arc 1.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 16:25:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Arc 2]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>asdasd]]></description><link>Timeline\Arc 2.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Timeline/Arc 2.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 12:42:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Prologue]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Io's time in the Lab. Escape plan is done, and Io and other test subjects execute their plan to escape. It is successful and they escape. They are split up by <a data-href="Lab Spies" href="\Characters\Lab Spies.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Lab Spies</a> chasing after them. Io travels down to the <a data-href="The Floor of Forest" href="\Locations\Floors\The Floor of Forest.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Floor of Forest</a>]]></description><link>Timeline\Prologue.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Timeline/Prologue.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 06:49:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Time]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The creation of the <a data-href="Celestial Spire" href="\Locations\Spire\Celestial Spire.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Celestial Spire</a> marked the start of the time period of]]></description><link>Timeline\Time.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Timeline/Time.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 06:47:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Home]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Homepage for the Celestial Spire World project. This project serves as a wiki for the Celestial Spire, documenting the worldbuilding and lore, with a general overview and notes about the story.<br><br><br><a data-href="Celestial Spire" href="\Locations\Spire\Celestial Spire.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Celestial Spire</a><br><br>Floor 1 - <a data-href="The Floor of Light" href="\Locations\Floors\The Floor of Light.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Floor of Light</a><br>
Floor 2 - <a data-href="The Floor of Ice" href="\Locations\Floors\The Floor of Ice.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Floor of Ice</a><br>
Floor 3 - <a data-href="The Floor of Shadows" href="\Locations\Floors\The Floor of Shadows.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Floor of Shadows</a><br>
Floor 4 - <a data-href="The Floor of Water" href="\Locations\Floors\The Floor of Water.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Floor of Water</a><br>
Floor 5 - <a data-href="The Floor of Forest" href="\Locations\Floors\The Floor of Forest.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Floor of Forest</a><br>
Floor 6 - <a data-href="The Floor of Sand" href="\Locations\Floors\The Floor of Sand.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Floor of Sand</a><br>
Floor 7 - <a data-href="The Floor of Fire" href="\Locations\Floors\The Floor of Fire.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Floor of Fire</a><br><br><a data-href="Gris" href="\Characters\Gris.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Gris</a><br>
<a data-href="The Entity" href="\Characters\The Entity.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Entity</a><br>
<a data-href="Scout" href="\Characters\Scout.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Scout</a><br>
<a data-href="Iota" href="\Characters\Iota.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Iota</a><br>
<a data-href="Yuki" href="\Characters\Yuki.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Yuki</a><br>
<a data-href="Ray" href="\Characters\Ray.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Ray</a><br><br><a data-href="Adventurer's Guild" href="\Factions\Guilds\Adventurer's Guild.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Adventurer's Guild</a><br>
<a data-href="Courier's Guild" href="\Factions\Guilds\Courier's Guild.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Courier's Guild</a><br><br><a data-href="Magic" href="\Magic\Magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Magic</a>]]></description><link>Home.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Home.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 12:39:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>